MkvDrama.net
MkvDrama.net
[This program is intended for mature audiences aged 18 and over]
[هذا البرنامج مخصص للجمهور الناضج الذي يبلغ عمره 18 عامًا فأكثر]
[It may contain explicit visuals, audio,
[قد يحتوي على صور ومقاطع صوتية صريحة،
behavior, intense violence, sexual content, and strong language]
السلوك والعنف الشديد والمحتوى الجنسي واللغة القوية]
[Viewer discretion is advised]
[ينصح المشاهدين بالحذر]
[This series is entirely fictional]
[هذه السلسلة خيالية تمامًا]
[It is not based on, nor intended to represent,
[إنه لا يعتمد على، ولا يهدف إلى تمثيل،
any real individuals or organizations]
أي أفراد أو منظمات حقيقية]
You didn't get any sleep last night?
لم تحصل على أي نوم الليلة الماضية؟
I'm feeling bad
انا اشعر بالسوء
knowing you and your mother fought.
مع العلم أنك وأمك تقاتلتم.
How about...
ماذا عن...
today,
اليوم،
you go talk things out with her?
هل تذهب للتحدث معها؟
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
she would understand
انها سوف تفهم
if I told her
لو قلت لها
I don't want to be an actress
لا أريد أن أكون ممثلة
or waste my time
أو أضيع وقتي
on something that isn't right for me?
على شيء لا يناسبني؟
I've made my decision, Print.
لقد اتخذت قراري، اطبع.
I want to be a director.
أريد أن أصبح مخرجًا.
If, one day...
إذا، في يوم من الأيام...
Mother sees my success,
أمي ترى نجاحي،
I believe she will come around.
أعتقد أنها سوف تتحسن.
If this is what you decided on,
إذا كان هذا هو ما قررته،
then go for it.
ثم اذهب لذلك.
I'll be your biggest supporter!
سأكون أكبر داعم لك!
Hello!
مرحبًا!
Print!
مطبعة!
Check out the news, now!
تابعوا الأخبار الآن!
Alright, alright...
حسنًا، حسنًا...
The newest rising star, Print Panwarin,
أحدث النجم الصاعد، Print Panwarin،
who is a front-runner for the Best New Actor award,
من هو المرشح الأوفر حظًا لجائزة أفضل ممثل جديد؟
is now seemingly
يبدو الآن
facing a serious allegation of a skincare hoax
مواجهة ادعاء خطير بشأن خدعة العناية بالبشرة
related to "Actress P."
ذات صلة ب "الممثلة P."
Here's the story:
وهنا القصة:
this scandal involves Actress P,
تتعلق هذه الفضيحة بالممثلة بي،
whose past photos are being exposed by netizens,
الذين تم الكشف عن صورهم السابقة من قبل مستخدمي الإنترنت،
revealing that she posted reviews of said skincare on her social media.
وكشفت أنها نشرت مراجعات للعناية بالبشرة على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي الخاصة بها.
This has caused immense damage so far.
وقد تسبب هذا في أضرار جسيمة حتى الآن.
The GL project that was just announced
مشروع GL الذي تم الإعلان عنه للتو
is bombarded with comments to switch Print out of the cast.
يتم قصفها بالتعليقات للتبديل الطباعة خارج المدلى بها.
[These money-hungry influencers need to be canceled]
[ يجب إلغاء هؤلاء المؤثرين المتعطشين للمال ]
Right after I knew the skincare was a scam,
بعد أن عرفت أن العناية بالبشرة كانت عملية احتيال،
I deleted all the posts,
لقد حذفت جميع المشاركات
canceled all the sales, and recalled all the products.
تم إلغاء كافة المبيعات وسحب كافة المنتجات.
It does seem strange...
يبدو غريبا حقا...
This was a while ago; why is it being exposed now?
لقد كان هذا منذ فترة طويلة، فلماذا يتم الكشف عنه الآن؟
It's because of me.
إنه بسببي.
Mother must be displeased,
يجب أن تكون الأم مستاءة،
so she chose to go with this...
لذلك اختارت أن تذهب مع هذا...
I'll talk to her.
سأتحدث معها.
It's no use, Rey.
لا فائدة من ذلك، ري.
In any case, it's partly my fault.
على أية حال، إنه خطئي جزئيا.
Print...
مطبعة...
First of all,
أولاً،
I would like to apologize to all the victims
وأود أن أعتذر لجميع الضحايا
and admit that I am partly responsible for the matter.
وأعترف بأنني مسؤول جزئيا عن هذا الأمر.
I truly am sorry.
أنا آسف حقا.
To control any more damage done by my past actions,
للسيطرة على أي ضرر آخر سببته أفعالي الماضية،
I have come to a conclusion with the director
لقد توصلت إلى نتيجة مع المخرج
to withdraw from my role as a presenter of all products,
الانسحاب من دوري كمقدم لجميع المنتجات،
along with the GL project
مع مشروع GL
that I took on with Rey.
التي قمت بها مع ري.
And who will be Rey's partner, then?
ومن سيكون شريك ري إذن؟
Have you had anyone in mind?
هل كان في ذهنك شخص ما؟
Will the project be canceled?
هل سيتم إلغاء المشروع؟
- What's the future of it? - Please answer.
- ما هو مستقبله؟ - أرجو الإجابة.
Is the project even gonna proceed?
هل المشروع سوف يمضي قدما؟
[A sloppy influencer like her deserves it]
[مؤثرة مهملة مثلها تستحق ذلك]
[Director Searching for Replacement, Rey May Lose Lead]
[المخرج يبحث عن بديل، ري قد يخسر دور البطولة]
[No one's perfect; at least Print owned up to it]
[لا أحد مثالي؛ على الأقل اعترفت برينت بذلك]
[Lots of love for Print]
[الكثير من الحب للطباعة]
Even by doing this,
حتى من خلال القيام بهذا،
Rey's not gonna come back.
ري لن يعود.
Not now,
ليس الآن،
but maybe later.
ولكن ربما في وقت لاحق.
I've given her the best treatment.
لقد قدمت لها أفضل معاملة.
It's a good thing she'll now live her life
من الجيد أنها ستعيش حياتها الآن
so that she realizes what it's like without me.
حتى تدرك كيف هي الحياة بدوني.
This is exactly the reason
هذا هو السبب بالضبط
why no one can stand you.
لماذا لا أحد يستطيع أن يتحملك.
I see how much you love playing the nice parent
أرى كم تحب لعب دور الوالد اللطيف
while making me the evil, controlling one,
بينما يجعلني الشرير المسيطر،
even though you're not any better.
حتى لو لم تكن أفضل.
Why is my good girl looking so stressed out?
لماذا تبدو فتاتي الطيبة متوترة للغاية؟
You haven't memorized all the lines?
لم تحفظ جميع السطور؟
This is the script for the movie you play with Nicha!
هذا هو السيناريو للفيلم الذي تلعبه مع نيشا!
I'm so excited for you!
أنا متحمس جدًا لك!
Hm?
هممم؟
I feel terrible
انا اشعر بالرعب
that I'm the only one with all this work,
أنني الوحيد الذي لديه كل هذا العمل،
even though...
بالرغم من...
you auditioned for this role.
لقد قمت بالاختبار لهذا الدور.
Aw,
حسنًا،
this role?
هذا الدور؟
If a rising star like you had done the audition,
إذا كان نجم صاعد مثلك قد أجرى الاختبار،
you would've nailed it, too!
لقد كنت قد نجحت في ذلك أيضًا!
Stop being so upset.
توقف عن الانزعاج.
Come on, let's see your 5000-dollar smile.
تعال، دعنا نرى ابتسامتك التي تبلغ قيمتها 5000 دولار.
Who in the world could smile in this situation?
من في العالم يستطيع أن يبتسم في هذا الموقف؟
Was that reason enough to make you smile?
هل كان هذا السبب كافيا لجعلك تبتسم؟
There you go!
ها أنت ذا!
With this big smile,
مع هذه الابتسامة الكبيرة،
I guess you can help me with something, Rey?
أعتقد أنه يمكنك مساعدتي في شيء ما، ري؟
With my open schedule,
مع جدول أعمالي المفتوح،
I will go through auditions after auditions.
سأخضع لاختبارات الأداء تلو الأخرى.
Can you give me suggestions, Miss Rising Star?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني اقتراحات، يا نجمة الصاعدة؟
First,
أولاً،
if you're sure the casting director doesn't have an outfit for you,
إذا كنت متأكدًا من أن مدير اختيار الممثلين ليس لديه ملابس مناسبة لك،
you need to bring one that fits the character.
يجب عليك إحضار ما يتناسب مع الشخصية.
Like this?
مثله؟
Print!
مطبعة!
You're auditioning for someone disguised as a man.
أنت تقوم بتجربة أداء لشخص متنكر في هيئة رجل.
This color won't work!
هذا اللون لن يعمل!
So...
لذا...
does my bra still work?
هل حمالة الصدر الخاصة بي لا تزال تعمل؟
Print!
مطبعة!
Ugh!
اه!
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
Being this free doesn't feel right...
إن كونك حرًا إلى هذه الدرجة لا يبدو صحيحًا...
I'm not used to it at all, Mai.
أنا لست معتادة على ذلك على الإطلاق، ماي.
- Uh... - Hm?
- اه... - همم؟
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
is Rey really gonna focus on being a director?
هل حقا سوف يركز ري على أن يكون مخرجا؟
Print said she hadn't had much work lately
قالت برينت إنها لم تحصل على الكثير من العمل مؤخرًا
and that I should rest while I could.
وأنني يجب أن أستريح بينما أستطيع.
Also...
أيضًا...
she mentioned
ذكرت
that I should spend this time with you.
أن أقضي هذا الوقت معك.
I guess Facebook really is spying on users...
أعتقد أن الفيسبوك يتجسس على المستخدمين حقًا...
I said the word 'vacation' once,
لقد قلت كلمة "إجازة" مرة واحدة،
and here come a hundred different plane ticket ads.
وهنا تأتي مائة إعلان مختلف لتذاكر الطائرات.
Were you talking to me?
هل كنت تتحدث معي؟
I said
قلت
Print told me to spend time with you.
طلبت مني الطباعة أن أقضي وقتًا معك.
Ah...
اه...
That's nice.
هذا جميل.
Ahem!
أهم!
Ahem! Ahem!
أهـم! أهـم!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Is your throat dry? I'll get you some water.
هل حلقك جاف؟ سأحضر لك بعض الماء.
My throat is not dry!!
حلقي ليس جافًا!!
Perfect places in Bangkok to go on a date.
أماكن مثالية في بانكوك للذهاب في موعد.
Going on dates improves a relationship.
إن الذهاب في مواعيد غرامية يحسن العلاقة.
Phone addiction can be deadly;
إدمان الهاتف قد يكون قاتلاً؛
engaging in activities is recommended!
يُنصح بالمشاركة في الأنشطة!
[Romantic trips for lovebirds]
[رحلات رومانسية للعشاق]
"A ceramic class for couples."
"دورة سيراميك للأزواج."
"Take your date on a one-day trip in Bangkok."
"خذ شريكك في رحلة لمدة يوم واحد في بانكوك."
There's the spying. It's real.
هناك تجسس. إنه حقيقي.
Mai...
أكثر...
Yes, baby?
نعم حبيبي؟
Since we have the same free time,
بما أن لدينا نفس وقت الفراغ،
don't you think we should make a plan for something?
ألا تعتقد أنه يجب علينا أن نضع خطة لشيء ما؟
Sounds great.
يبدو رائعا.
I also have some plans myself.
لدي أيضًا بعض الخطط لنفسي.
What is it, babe?
ما الأمر يا حبيبتي؟
I'm planning on...
أنا أخطط ل...
starting my own company.
بدء شركتي الخاصة.
Are you for real right now?
هل أنت حقيقي الآن؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Isn't it a good thing?
أليس هذا شيئاً جيداً؟
I didn't mean those kinds of plans!
لم أقصد هذا النوع من الخطط!
And what plans did you mean?
وما هي الخطط التي تقصدها؟
Ugh!
اه!
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
Apart from being good in bed, are you always this naive?!
بصرف النظر عن كونك جيدًا في السرير، هل أنت ساذج دائمًا إلى هذه الدرجة؟!
Stop with those puppy eyes!
توقف عن تلك العيون الجرو!
You were the one telling me to move in
لقد كنت أنت من طلب مني أن أتحرك
so that we could spend more time together.
حتى نتمكن من قضاء المزيد من الوقت معًا.
Look at your so-called 'vacation.'
أنظر إلى ما يسمى بـ "إجازتك".
You haven't been away from the work on your phone!
لم تكن بعيدًا عن العمل على هاتفك!
Is this what you called spending time together?
هل هذا ما تسميه قضاء الوقت معًا؟
Then, let's go on a date today
إذن، دعنا نذهب في موعد اليوم
without thinking about work
دون التفكير في العمل
or touching our phones.
أو لمس هواتفنا.
I'll nail it without breaking a sweat.
سأقوم بذلك دون بذل أي جهد.
Are you even built for this?
هل أنت مؤهل لهذا؟
Bring it on.
اجلبه.
Though I look like a workaholic,
على الرغم من أنني أبدو وكأنني مدمن عمل،
I know about work-life balance.
أنا أعرف عن التوازن بين العمل والحياة.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- نعم نعم.
Hey!
يا!
[Rey: I've arrived on set]
[ري: لقد وصلت إلى المجموعة]
You're here, Rey?
أنت هنا، ري؟
Hi, Nicha.
مرحباً، نيشا.
Hi there.
أهلاً.
Thank you, ma'am.
شكرا لك سيدتي.
I'm so happy
انا سعيد للغاية
that you'll play the role of my daughter.
أنك ستلعب دور ابنتي.
I feel the same having the chance to work with you.
أشعر بنفس الشعور عندما أتيحت لي الفرصة للعمل معك.
Look,
ينظر،
if you need any help,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي مساعدة،
don't hesitate to tell me.
لا تتردد في أن تخبرني.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Sir!
سيد!
I'm here for a job interview.
أنا هنا لإجراء مقابلة عمل.
There's no reason to be nice when you're evil.
ليس هناك سبب لأن تكون لطيفًا عندما تكون شريرًا.
And we...will reunite again
ونحن... سوف نلتقي مرة أخرى
on the Milky...
على الحليب...
Cut!
يقطع!
Wow.
رائع.
She's amazing.
إنها مذهلة.
She really is.
إنها كذلك حقا.
I'll contact you later.
سأتصل بك لاحقا.
Thank you very much, Print.
شكرا جزيلا لك، طباعة.
Please go ahead that way.
من فضلك إذهب إلى الأمام بهذه الطريقة.
Who the heck called her for the audition?
من الذي اتصل بها للاختبار؟
Isn't she the one with that fresh scandal?
أليست هي صاحبة الفضيحة الجديدة؟
Do you want our project to be screwed?
هل تريد أن يتم إفساد مشروعنا؟
Jeez.
جيز.
Ahem!
أهم!
We made a promise, didn't we?
لقد قطعنا وعدًا، أليس كذلك؟
I was just...
لقد كنت فقط...
putting it on silent mode.
وضعه على الوضع الصامت.
Well, do it.
حسنا، افعلها.
Okay!
تمام!
- Is it on silent? - Mm...
- هل هو صامت؟ - مم...
Then,
ثم،
I'll keep it safe for you.
سأبقيه آمنًا لك.
- Now, get back to teaching! - Alright, baby.
- الآن عودي إلى التدريس! - حسنًا يا عزيزتي.
Put your hand here.
ضع يدك هنا.
You did an amazing job in that scene, Rey.
لقد قمت بعمل مذهل في هذا المشهد، ري.
I'm not surprised
أنا لست متفاجئا
that you've become a top-tier actress at such a young age.
أنك أصبحت ممثلة من الدرجة الأولى في مثل هذا العمر الصغير.
All thanks to you, Nicha, for your emotional delivery.
كل الشكر لك، نيشا، على توصيلك العاطفي.
For a second there, I thought you were my real mother.
لفترة وجيزة، اعتقدت أنك والدتي الحقيقية.
I'm getting pretty hungry.
أنا أشعر بالجوع جدًا.
What should we eat?
ماذا يجب أن نأكل؟
What do you want to have?
ماذا تريد أن تحصل عليه؟
How about we make something at home?
ماذا عن أن نصنع شيئاً في المنزل؟
There are seven days in a week,
هناك سبعة أيام في الأسبوع،
and yet we dine in eight days a week.
ومع ذلك فإننا نتناول العشاء ثمانية أيام في الأسبوع.
I'm bored of that.
لقد سئمت من ذلك.
It'd be nice to dine out once in a while!
سيكون من الجميل أن نتناول الطعام خارجًا من حين لآخر!
Uh...
أوه...
Then,
ثم،
give me my phone.
أعطني هاتفي.
I'll look up something nice to eat around here.
سأبحث عن شيء لطيف لأكله هنا.
Fine.
بخير.
Only for searching for restaurants, though.
فقط للبحث عن المطاعم، على الرغم من ذلك.
I'll go to the restroom real quick. I'll be right back.
سأذهب إلى الحمام بسرعة. سأعود حالًا.
"Send the file ASAP."
"أرسل الملف في أقرب وقت ممكن."
Why now?
لماذا الان؟
- Oh... - Argh!
- أوه... - أرغ!
Ouch!
آخ!
Mai, what in the world are you doing?
ماي، ماذا تفعلين في العالم؟
I lost my contact lens.
لقد فقدت عدساتي اللاصقة.
- Huh? - Yeah...
- هاه؟ - نعم...
How did you even lose it?
كيف فقدته؟
Wait...
انتظر...
I think we should head back to the office.
أعتقد أننا يجب أن نعود إلى المكتب.
Just to put my contact lens back on, alright?
فقط لإعادة وضع عدساتي اللاصقة، حسنًا؟
Alright, fine. Let's go.
حسناً، حسناً. لنذهب.
It stings.
إنه يلسع.
- This way. - This?
- من هنا. - هذا؟
- I said this way! - Alright, alright.
- قلت هذا الطريق! - حسنًا، حسنًا.
Fon!
نعم!
Just wait here.
فقط انتظر هنا.
I'll just take a sec to put it back on.
سأستغرق ثانية واحدة فقط لوضعه مرة أخرى.
Be right back.
سأعود.
Fon!
نعم!
If anyone ever asks...
إذا سأل أحد يوما ما...
what your girlfriend's name is,
ما اسم صديقتك؟
are you gonna say it's "Work"?
هل ستقول أنها "عمل"؟
It's...
إنه...
an urgent matter, Fon.
مسألة عاجلة، فون.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
white flag.
العلم الأبيض.
I admit I broke our deal today.
أعترف أنني خالفت اتفاقنا اليوم.
Mai,
يمكن،
do you think that I asked you on a date
هل تعتقد أنني طلبت منك موعدًا؟
just because I wanna win?
فقط لأنني أريد الفوز؟
Do you think this is a competition?
هل تعتقد أن هذه مسابقة؟
I'm not...
انا لست...
I don't wanna defeat you like I did before!
لا أريد أن أهزمك كما فعلت من قبل!
- I really want to spend time with you! - No...
- أريد حقًا قضاء الوقت معك! - لا...
I understand now.
انا أفهم الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Do you think I'm that easy?
هل تعتقد أنني بهذه السهولة؟
You think you'll win me over with a simple apology?
هل تعتقد أنك ستفوز بي باعتذار بسيط؟
Fon...
تمويل...
how can I make it up to you?
كيف يمكنني تعويضك؟
Hm?
هممم؟
How?
كيف؟
Don't be mad at me, please?
لا تغضب مني من فضلك؟
Does this work?
هل هذا يعمل؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm very sorry.
انا اسف جدا.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Forgive me, pretty please?
سامحني من فضلك؟
Cut it. Stay still.
اقطعها. ابق ساكنًا.
A bad girl
فتاة سيئة
must be punished.
يجب معاقبته.
[I won't break another promise]
[لن أخلف وعدًا آخر]
Sign it.
توقيعه.
You're home, Rey?
أنت في المنزل، ري؟
Can we just stay like this for a while?
هل يمكننا البقاء على هذا الحال لفترة من الوقت؟
My wishes didn't work, did they?
أمنياتي لم تتحقق، أليس كذلك؟
Look at how negative my image is now.
انظر إلى مدى سلبية صورتي الآن.
No one's interested in what I can offer anymore!
لم يعد أحد مهتمًا بما أستطيع تقديمه بعد الآن!
If they're not interested in you here,
إذا لم يكونوا مهتمين بك هنا،
then...
ثم...
should we go somewhere else?
هل يجب علينا أن نذهب إلى مكان آخر؟
Somewhere else?
مكان آخر؟
Nicha recommended me a film by a Korean producer.
لقد أوصتني نيشا بفيلم لمنتج كوري.
If you're interested,
إذا كنت مهتما،
we gotta send them an audition video.
يتعين علينا أن نرسل لهم فيديو الاختبار.
But it's already midnight, Rey.
لكن الوقت الآن منتصف الليل، ري.
If I force it,
إذا أجبرته،
will it even turn out well?
هل ستكون النتيجة جيدة؟
It depends on...
يعتمد على...
if you want me to be your personal director.
إذا كنت تريدني أن أكون مديرك الشخصي.
If you're my personal director,
إذا كنت مديري الشخصي،
there's no need to pay me a dime.
ليس هناك حاجة لدفع لي سنتا واحدا.
All I ask for is a little support...
كل ما أطلبه هو القليل من الدعم...
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Three, two, one...
ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد...
And, action!
و العمل!
Without you by my side,
بدونك بجانبي
how am I supposed to live?
كيف من المفترض أن أعيش؟
Without me by your side,
بدوني بجانبك،
your life might be easier.
ربما تصبح حياتك أسهل.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
My life...
حياتي...
would be just as before you came in
سيكون كما كان قبل مجيئك
Just me by mysef
أنا فقط من قبل mysef
When everything was simplier
عندما كان كل شيء أبسط
I could do whatever I wanted
كان بإمكاني أن أفعل ما أريد
whenever I wanted
كلما أردت
More peaceful
أكثر سلمية
...and far less chaotic
...وأقل فوضوية بكثير
But...
لكن...
I wouldn’t be as happy as I am now
لن أكون سعيدًا كما أنا الآن
Thank you...
شكرًا لك...
for fulfilling my life
لتحقيق أهدافي في الحياة
with so much meaning.
مع الكثير من المعنى.
Okay!
تمام!
You...
أنت...
are the greatest blessing in my life.
هم أعظم نعمة في حياتي.
Is it bad?
هل هو سيء؟
Print...
مطبعة...
that was an amazing performance!
لقد كان أداء مذهلا!
How come you slay so hard?!
كيف تقتل بهذه القوة؟!
Girl!
بنت!
- Darn! - Gosh,
- يا إلهي! - يا إلهي،
Fon, you're so extra.
فون، أنت إضافي جدًا.
I'm not!
انا لا!
Your acting was epic!
لقد كان تمثيلك ملحميًا!
Be more confident in yourself.
كن أكثر ثقة في نفسك.
And when will you know the result?
ومتى ستعرف النتيجة؟
As far as I know, within this month.
حسب علمي، خلال هذا الشهر.
But I don't know if it's gonna make the cut.
لكنني لا أعلم إذا كان سينجح.
Girlie,
بناتي،
stop overthinking it.
توقف عن التفكير الزائد في الأمر.
I think you have a shot,
أعتقد أن لديك فرصة
considering you're a front-runner for the Best New Actor award.
مع الأخذ في الاعتبار أنك من المرشحين الأوفر حظًا لجائزة أفضل ممثل جديد.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
cheers!
هتافات!
Rey!
ري!
What are you doing out here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
You'll get eaten alive by the mosquitoes.
سوف تأكلك البعوض حيًا.
If you won the award,
إذا فزت بالجائزة،
what would be your acceptance speech?
ما هو خطاب قبولك؟
Hm...
هممم...
I guess that never crossed my mind.
أعتقد أن هذا لم يخطر ببالي أبدًا.
I'm not even sure I'll get it.
أنا لست متأكدة حتى من أنني سأحصل عليه.
Have you heard about manifestation?
هل سمعت عن التجلي؟
Word is...
الكلمة هي...
if you envision something vividly in your head,
إذا كنت تتخيل شيئًا واضحًا في رأسك،
it might come true one day.
ربما يتحقق ذلك يوما ما.
This award
هذه الجائزة
is not only a declaration of my position as the Best Actress,
ليس مجرد إعلان عن مكانتي كأفضل ممثلة،
but it is also
لكنها أيضا
a testament to all my dedication
شهادة على كل تفاني
and effort,
والجهد
as well as that of the staff from The Doll Mansion.
وكذلك طاقم عمل The Doll Mansion.
I would like to share this award with the crew,
وأود أن أشارك هذه الجائزة مع الطاقم،
those who never leave my side,
أولئك الذين لا يتركون جانبي أبدًا،
and those that I love.
والذين أحبهم.
This award...
هذه الجائزة...
also belongs to Print.
تنتمي أيضًا إلى الطباعة.
Wait a sec.
انتظر ثانية.
Are you really gonna go all out?
هل حقا سوف تبذل كل ما في وسعك؟
No,
لا،
it's just...
إنه فقط...
I can't say all this on the stage,
لا أستطيع أن أقول كل هذا على المسرح،
so I want to say it to you today, Print.
لذا أريد أن أقولها لك اليوم، يا برينت.
Mm!
مم!
Can I ask you something?
هل يمكننى ان اسألك شيئا؟
Are you really not gonna talk to your mother?
هل حقا لن تتحدث مع والدتك؟
I know that,
وأنا أعلم ذلك،
in reality,
في الواقع،
you also feel bad
أنت تشعر بالسوء أيضا
for leaving her like this.
لتركها هكذا.
Are you not angry at her?
هل أنت غاضب منها؟
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
Think of it this way:
فكر في الأمر بهذه الطريقة:
what would you do
ماذا ستفعل؟
if someone's the reason your daughter gives up her future,
إذا كان شخص ما هو السبب في تخلي ابنتك عن مستقبلها،
refuses to work abroad,
يرفض العمل في الخارج،
and abandons her dream entirely?
وتتخلى عن حلمها كليا؟
If that were me,
لو كنت أنا،
I'd also hate their guts.
أنا أيضا أكره أحشائهم.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mai, where are you? I'm already here.
ماي، أين أنتِ؟ أنا هنا بالفعل.
#Supphanikarn2025
#Supphanikarn2025
[Father of famous celeb spotted on a date with renowned actress #Supphanikarn2025Gossip]
[تم رصد والد أحد المشاهير في موعد مع الممثلة الشهيرة #Supphanikarn2025Gossip]
[Bye “Happy Family” Hello “Broken Home”]
وداعًا يا عائلة سعيدة؟ أهلاً يا بيت مكسور؟
[It’s OVER. Rey’s family in shambles]
انتهى الأمر. عائلة ري في حالة يرثى لها.
[Wife VS Mistress. Who will win?]
[الزوجة ضد العشيقة. من سيفوز؟]
[Hope Rey recover from hot mess]
[أتمنى أن يتعافى ري من الفوضى الساخنة]
Did you see the news on Twitter?
هل رأيت الخبر على تويتر؟
I did, Sis. That was brutal!
لقد فعلتُ ذلك يا أختي. كان ذلك وحشي!
I feel so bad for Rey.
أنا أشعر بالأسف الشديد تجاه ري.
Feel bad about what?
أشعر بالسوء بشأن ماذا؟
Wanmai!
رائع!
What is this about?
ما هذا؟
Does Mother...
هل الأم...
Does Mother know?
هل الأم تعرف؟
Miss Duen already knows about this, Rey.
السيدة دوان تعرف هذا بالفعل، ري.
And why...
ولماذا...
The reason she puts up with it
السبب الذي يجعلها تتحمل ذلك
and hasn't filed for a divorce
ولم يتقدم بطلب الطلاق
is that she's afraid she couldn't take care of you.
إنها خائفة من أنها لن تتمكن من الاعتناء بك.
She's afraid...
إنها خائفة...
your father's side of the family will cut you off,
سوف يقطعك جانب والدك من العائلة،
especially your grandfather,
وخاصة جدك
who never accepted your mother to begin with.
الذي لم يقبل والدتك منذ البداية.
And the reason she forces her dream on you
والسبب الذي يجعلها تفرض حلمها عليك
is not only because of herself.
ليس فقط بسبب نفسها.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Rey, thank the teacher.
ري، أشكر المعلم.
But she wants them to accept you.
لكنها تريد منهم أن يقبلوك.
She's always worried about you.
إنها قلقة عليك دائمًا.
She calls me to check on you all the time.
إنها تتصل بي للاطمئنان عليك طوال الوقت.
Rey!
ري!
I want to see Mother...
أريد أن أرى أمي...
Please be on standby in 10 minutes.
يرجى أن تكون على أهبة الاستعداد في غضون 10 دقائق.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to...
سيداتي وسادتي، مرحباً بكم في...
the 2025 Supannikarn Award Ceremony.
حفل توزيع جوائز Supannikarn لعام 2025.
It's finally the moment everyone's waiting for...
إنها أخيرا اللحظة التي ينتظرها الجميع...
The announcement of the Best Actress of the Year.
الإعلان عن جائزة أفضل ممثلة لهذا العام.
We will now find out
سوف نكتشف الآن
which actress gives the most touching performance
أي ممثلة قدمت الأداء الأكثر إثارة للمشاعر؟
this year.
هذا العام.
As for this moment,
أما في هذه اللحظة،
I hereby welcome Miss Asamapon Samakphan,
أرحب هنا بالآنسة أسامابون ساماكفان،
last year's Best Actress
أفضل ممثلة في العام الماضي
to please honor us by presenting the award.
من فضلك قم بتكريمنا بتقديم الجائزة.
Alright...
على ما يرام...
The 2025 Best Actress
أفضل ممثلة لعام 2025
goes to...
يذهب إلى...
Miss Rey Radubdao
الآنسة راي رادوباو
from The Doll Mansion!
من قصر الدمى!
Congratulations!
مبروك!
Congratulations.
مبروك.
- Thank you. - My pleasure.
- شكرا لك. - يسعدني ذلك.
As a child,
عندما كنت طفلا،
I used to stand in front of a mirror
كنت أقف أمام المرآة
with a bottle of water in my hand,
مع زجاجة ماء في يدي،
practicing my award acceptance speech.
أتدرب على خطاب قبول الجائزة.
But now that the day has arrived,
ولكن الآن وقد جاء اليوم،
all those fancy words just disappear from my head.
كل هذه الكلمات الفاخرة تختفي من رأسي.
All that's left now
كل ما تبقى الآن
is how thankful I am
كم أنا ممتن
for Pong, the director,
بالنسبة للمخرج بونج،
and the crew members of The Doll Mansion.
وأعضاء طاقم The Doll Mansion.
Thank you, everyone, for your support.
شكرا للجميع على دعمكم.
Most importantly,
والأهم من ذلك كله،
I wanna thank the person who has always supported me,
وأريد أن أشكر الشخص الذي دعمني دائمًا،
taken the time to push me forward,
لقد أخذ الوقت الكافي لدفعي للأمام،
and put up with everything for my sake.
وتحمل كل شيء من أجلي.
Without her,
بدونها
I wouldn't...
انا لا ارغب في ذلك
I wouldn't be here.
لن أكون هنا.
Thank you, Mother,
شكرا لك يا أمي
for everything you've done for me.
لكل ما فعلته من أجلي.
Without you...
بدونك...
I wouldn't be who I am today.
لن أكون كما أنا اليوم.
For that reason,
ولهذا السبب،
this award
هذه الجائزة
is not only mine,
ليس لي وحدي،
but my mother's, too.
ولكن والدتي أيضًا.
Right,
يمين،
how was your mother's hospital visit?
كيف كانت زيارة والدتك للمستشفى؟
Why?
لماذا؟
If you're worried, why don't you ask me directly?
إذا كنت قلقًا، لماذا لا تسألني بشكل مباشر؟
- Uh... - Hm?
- اه... - همم؟
Sorry, Mother...
عذرا يا أمي...
I mean, Auntie.
أعني، عمتي.
I...
أنا...
I didn't know you were coming along,
لم أكن أعلم أنك قادم
- so I... - So you what?
- إذًا أنا... - إذن ماذا؟
You don't want me here?
ألا تريدني هنا؟
It's not like that! You can come...
ليس الأمر كذلك! يمكنك المجيء...
So...what brings you here, Auntie?
إذن... ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا يا عمتي؟
I just want to pay a visit to my daughter's girlfriend's home.
أريد فقط أن أزور منزل صديقة ابنتي.
"My daughter's girlfriend"?!
"صديقة ابنتي"؟!
Mother, please stop teasing her.
أمي، من فضلك توقفي عن مضايقتها.
She's all shaken up.
لقد اهتزت كلها.
I never knew my daughter-in-law is easily scared.
لم أكن أعلم أبدًا أن زوجة ابني تخاف بسهولة.
I thought you were the spicy kind.
اعتقدت أنك من النوع الحار.
Auntie!
عمة!
"Mother."
"الأم."
Pardon?
عفو؟
Whoever told you to call me Auntie?
من قال لك أن تناديني عمتي؟
Take care of Rey for me.
اعتني بـراي من أجلي.
And I apologize for everything in the past.
وأنا أعتذر عن كل شيء في الماضي.
Of course, Mother!
بالطبع يا أمي!
Mother!
الأم!
- Are you getting used to it? - I am!
- هل اعتدت على ذلك؟ - أنا كذلك!
I think we should have someone fix Print's hair.
أعتقد أننا يجب أن نطلب من شخص ما إصلاح شعر برينت.
Toei, go take a look at Print's hair, please?
توي، اذهب وألقي نظرة على شعر برينت، من فضلك؟
Got it.
فهمتها.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- تفضل. - شكرا لك.
- How does it look now? - Good.
- كيف يبدو الآن؟ - جيد.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Alright, we're gonna start now.
حسنًا، سنبدأ الآن.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Five, four,
خمسة، أربعة،
three, two, one...
ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد...
Please welcome, Print and Rey!
من فضلك، مرحبًا بالطباعة وراي!
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hi, and welcome back.
مرحباً بك مرة أخرى.
I'll just cut to the chase.
سأقطع فقط إلى صلب الموضوع.
Last time, you told us
في المرة الماضية قلت لنا
you were besties,
لقد كنتم أفضل الأصدقاء،
but, from the look of it...
ولكن من مظهره...
I'm smelling something sus...
أنا أشم رائحة شيء ما
Can you tell us loud and clear
هل يمكنك أن تخبرنا بصوت عال وواضح؟
what your relationship is?
ما هي علاقتك؟
Are you a shipped couple or a real couple?
هل أنتما زوجين مرسلين أم زوجين حقيقيين؟
We are...
نحن...
Traffic's at a dead stop, Print.
توقفت حركة المرور تمامًا، اطبع.
I think there's another crash by the next intersection.
أعتقد أن هناك حادثًا آخر عند التقاطع التالي.
Fon, I think it's time for plan B.
فون، أعتقد أن الوقت قد حان للخطة ب.
Alright!
على ما يرام!
Sir!
سيد!
Could you please give her a ride to this place?
هل بإمكانك من فضلك أن توصلها إلى هذا المكان؟
Just follow the navigation here.
فقط اتبع الملاحة هنا.
Alright, get on the back!
حسنًا، اصعد إلى الخلف!
Okay, go!
حسنا، اذهب!
See you there, Fon.
أراك هناك، فون.
Alright, sit tight!
حسنا، اجلس بهدوء!
- Ready? - Let's go, sir.
- مستعد؟ - دعنا نذهب، سيدي.